Why can't I use this voucher to pay for my purchases?
為什麼我不能使用此優惠券來支付我的購買費用？
I'm afraid it is no longer valid.
恐怕它不再有效了。
Discounts are not offered now.
現在不提供折扣。
You can pay at the check-out.
您可以在退房時付款。
The results of the survey praised everyone for their excellent customer service.
調查結果讚揚了每個人出色的客戶服務。
We try to give them a horrid shopping experience.
我們試圖為他們帶來可怕的購物體驗。
I'm surprised our prices were rated so highly.
我很驚訝我們的價格得到如此高的評價。
Customer satisfaction is the key to a good business.
客戶滿意度是良好業務的關鍵。
Questions 38 to 40 refer to the following conversation.
第38至40題涉及以下對話。
Excuse me, I'd like to return this camera.
對不起，我想退回這台相機。
May I ask what the problem is with it?
請問它有什麼問題嗎？
It's much too complicated to use.
使用起來太複雜了。
I cannot figure out how to do anything except turn it on.
除了打開它之外我不知道該怎麼做。
All right.
好的。
Did you bring your receipt with you?
你帶收據了嗎？
Yes, I have it right here.
是的，我這裡就有。
Oh, I'm sorry ma'am, but it looks like you used a discount coupon on the camera.
哦，對不起，女士，您似乎在相機上使用了折扣券。
Yes, that's right.
是的，沒錯。
I had a coupon for twenty percent off.
我有一張百分之二十折扣的優惠券。
Is that a problem?
這是一個問題嗎？
Unfortunately, because you used the coupon, we are unable to refund you the money.
很遺憾，由於您使用了優惠券，我們無法為您退款。
Are you kidding?
你在開玩笑吧？
That's ridiculous.
這太荒謬了。
I'm sorry.
對不起。
It's company policy.
這是公司政策。
What I can do though is have one of the sales representatives show you step-by-step how to operate the camera.
不過，我可以做的是讓一位銷售代表向您逐步展示如何操作相機。
Who most likely is the man?
這個男人最有可能是誰？
A fellow customer
一位顧客
A customer service representative
客戶服務代表
The regional sales manager
區域銷售經理
The front door store greeter
商店前門迎賓員
What does the woman say about the camera?
這位女士對相機有何評論？
She doesn't understand how to use it.
她不明白如何使用它。
It cannot hold a charge for more than an hour.
充電時間不能超過一個小時。
The included software is too complicated for her.
附帶的軟體對她來說太複雜了。
It will not turn on no matter what she does.
無論她做什麼，它都不會打開。
What does the man suggest that the woman do?
男人建議女人做什麼？
Figure out how to use it on her own.
弄清楚如何自己使用它。
Speak with his manager about a refund.
與他的經理討論退款事宜。
Use a coupon to buy a cheaper camera.
使用優惠券購買更便宜的相機。
Have an expert show her how to use it.
請專家向她展示如何使用它。
Questions 74 to 76 refer to the following announcement.
問題74至76請參閱以下公告。
Welcome shoppers.
歡迎各位購物者。
To celebrate our tenth anniversary, we are offering special discounts on a wide variety of items found in our store.
為了慶祝我們的十週年紀念日，我們對商店中的各種商品提供特別折扣。
To take advantage of this sale, all you need to do is download our app, and you'll automatically receive coupons for items in all departments such as clothing and electronics.
要利用這次促銷活動，您只需下載我們的應用程序，您就會自動收到服裝和電子產品等所有部門商品的優惠券。
Additionally, you can receive gifts if you spend three thousand, five thousand, and ten thousand dollars.
另外，消費滿三千、五千、一萬還可以獲得禮物。
These offers will only be available for the next two weeks, so don't miss out on the chance for some great deals!
這些優惠僅在接下來的兩週內提供，所以不要錯過一些超值優惠的機會！
Where would someone most likely hear this announcement?
人們最有可能在哪裡聽到此公告？
A department store
一家百貨公司
A convenience store
一家便利商店
A gardening supply store
一家園藝用品店
A home improvement store
一家家居裝修店
Who most likely are the listeners?
誰最有可能是聽眾？
The cashiers working at the registers.
收銀員在收銀台工作。
Managers in the main offices.
主要辦公室的經理。
Shoppers browsing and buying products
購物者瀏覽和購買產品
People walking by outside.
外面走過的人。
What does the speaker mean when he says "Don't miss out on the chance for some great deals!"?
當演講者說「不要錯過一些超值優惠的機會！」時，他的意思是什麼？
Customers are missing items from their orders.
客戶的訂單中缺少商品。
There is a last chance to get a free gift.
還有最後一次獲得免費禮物的機會。
People should quickly download the app.
人們應該快速下載該應用程式。
The deals are no longer being offered.
不再提供這些優惠。
In order to ensure that your order is fulfilled with as little delay as possible, be sure to place it a minimum of two weeks in advance.
為了確保您的訂單盡快滿足，請務必至少提前兩週下單。
little
小的
few
很少
neither
兩者都不
either
任何一個
Coupons for purchases may only be used for specific items in the store and will not be accepted if they are no longer valid.
購物優惠券只能用於商店內的特定商品，如果不再有效，將不再被接受。
continuously
不斷地
considered to be
被認為是
no longer
不再
as long as
只要
Replacement of any and all damaged parts, including the cost of repairs, is covered by the terms of the product warranty.
任何及所有損壞零件的更換（包括維修費用）均包含在產品保固條款內。
several
一些
all
全部
none
沒有任何
some
一些
Grand Opening!
盛大開幕！
Come celebrate the opening of the new Central Shopping Plaza on August 1st at ten thirty in the morning!
快來慶祝8月1日上午10點30分新中央購物廣場開幕！
Bring this coupon and enjoy a five percent discount on almost any purchase at most shops in the mall.
帶上這張優惠券，在商場的大多數商店購買幾乎所有商品均可享受 5% 的折扣。
The coupon is valid from August 1st, 2022 to August 31st, 2022.
此優惠券有效期限為2022年8月1日至2022年8月31日。
Some restrictions apply.
存在一些限制。
Coupons may not be used on home appliances or on items purchased at Spencer & Spencer's Gag Shop.
優惠券不可用於家用電器或在 Spencer & Spencer's Gag Shop 購買的商品。
Why is the Central Shopping Plaza offering discounts?
為什麼中央購物廣場有折扣？
To celebrate their anniversary.
為了慶祝他們的周年紀念日。
To clear out unsold items in stores.
清理商店中未售出的商品。
To celebrate the opening of the mall.
慶祝商場開幕。
To promote items exclusive to the mall.
促銷商場獨有的商品。
Under which circumstances would the coupon not be valid?
什麼情況下優惠券無效？
When buying a new oven.
購買新烤箱時。
When buying some clothing.
買一些衣服的時候。
When going on opening day.
開幕當天去的時候。
When purchasing sports shoes.
購買運動鞋時。
Grand Opening!
盛大開幕！
Come celebrate the grand opening of The Appliance Depot with us!
快來和我們一起慶祝The Appliance Depot盛大開幕吧！
We're so excited to bring you great deals on home appliances that we're practically giving them away for free.
我們很高興為您帶來家用電器的超值優惠，幾乎免費贈送。
From May 1st to May 31st just use one of the discount codes below on your purchase and you'll receive an incredible thirty percent off the sticker price.
從 5 月 1 日到 5 月 31 日，您只需在購買時使用以下折扣代碼之一，即可享受標價 30% 的令人難以置信的折扣。
That's right, thirty percent off!
沒錯，百分之三十的折扣！
And there's more!
還有更多！
Any order of home electronics over four hundred dollars will receive free door-to-door shipping, no matter where you are.
任何超過四百美元的家用電子產品訂單都將享有免費送貨上門服務，無論您身在何處。
To claim your discount coupon, simply log into your account and click on the coupon below.
要領取折扣優惠券，只需登入您的帳戶並點擊下面的優惠券即可。
The coupon will be added to your checkout options.
優惠券將添加到您的結帳選項中。
Just click on it when placing your order and it will automatically be applied to your total.
只需在下訂單時點擊它，它就會自動應用到您的總額中。
Orders that qualify for free shipping will automatically have the shipping fee waived.
符合免運費條件的訂單將自動免除運費。
Thirty Percent off any kitchen appliance price
任何廚房用具價格可享百分之三十的折扣
(Reference Number: KA349181) [Click Here]
（參考號：KA349181）[點此]
Thirty Percent off any home electronic price
任何家用電子產品價格可享百分之三十的折扣
(Reference Number: HE9703747) [Click Here]
(參考編號：HE9703747) [點此]
Thirty Percent off any lighting unit
任何照明裝置可享百分之三十的折扣
(Reference Number: LI37501840) [Click Here]
（參考編號：LI37501840）[點此]
To: customer_service@appliancedepot.com
至：customer_service@appliancedepot.com
From: hank2233@freemail.com
取自：hank2233@freemail.com
Subject: Shipping fee not waived
主題：運費不減免
Hi.
你好。
I'm trying to make a purchase of several items through your online shopping site, but I'm having a pretty serious problem.
我正在嘗試透過您的線上購物網站購買一些商品，但我遇到了一個非常嚴重的問題。
I'm trying to order a flatscreen television, XStation game console, and two controllers.
我正在嘗試訂購平板電視、XStation 遊戲機和兩個控制器。
The total comes to $670, after applying the discount code currently being offered.
使用目前提供的折扣代碼後，總金額為 670 美元。
As I understand it, these are considered home electronics, so according to the promotion you have going I should receive free shipping for them.
據我了解，這些被認為是家用電子產品，因此根據您正在進行的促銷活動，我應該為它們提供免費送貨。
However, every time I try to confirm the order and make the payment, the shipping fee is added onto the total.
但是，每次我嘗試確認訂單並付款時，運費都會添加到總額中。
Nothing I do can seem to waive the fee.
我所做的一切似乎都無法免除費用。
Please get back to me about this right away as tomorrow is the last day of the promotion and I would like to complete my order before then.
請立即回覆我，因為明天是促銷活動的最後一天，我想在此之前完成我的訂單。
Sincerely,
真摯地，
Hank Howards
漢克·霍華德
What is The Appliance Depot celebrating?
Appliance Depot 在慶祝什麼？
Thirty years of being in business.
從業三十年。
Opening their online shopping site.
打開他們的線上購物網站。
Their one-year anniversary.
他們一周年紀念日。
Opening a new branch location.
開設新分店。
What is mentioned about the discount codes?
折扣代碼提到了什麼？
Shoppers must log in to use them.
購物者必須登入才能使用它們。
They only apply to home appliances.
它們僅適用於家用電器。
Shoppers must enter the codes by themselves.
購物者必須自行輸入代碼。
They are good for a 50% discount.
它們有 50% 的折扣。
What is the problem Mr. Howards is having with his order?
霍華德先生的訂單有問題嗎？
The discount coupon does not work.
折扣券不起作用。
His payment method is not accepted.
他的付款方式不被接受。
The website keeps crashing on him.
他的網站總是崩潰。
He is incorrectly being charged a fee.
他被錯誤地收取了費用。
In the email, the word "waive" in paragraph 1, line 6 is closest in meaning to?
在電子郵件中，第 1 段第 6 行中的「放棄」一詞的含義最接近？
add
添加
decrease
減少
remove
消除
include
包括
On what date is Mr. Howards most likely making his purchase?
霍華德先生最有可能在哪一天購買？
May 1st
5月1日
May 29th
5月29日
May 30th
5月30日
May 31st
5月31日